He said it's a world of nothing.
I'll give you a kiss.
Sing only one phrase.
Just that one word.
How you can sing in a gutsy way is the key.
key to victory
In a moment of one phrase
put everything on the line
Strongest Singing Idol Grand Prix
Will it be the strongest singing idol's
Who will be crowned champion?
Now for the four contestants this time.
Three themes.
Singing ability and the ability to be an idol.
You will be competing against each other.
by the total score of all three rounds.
We will decide the winner.
In the limited short singing time
How you can promote yourself is the key.
It's the key to the game.
The theme of the first round is
Show off your singing ability.
is
And I'm going to ask you to sing.
The standard idol song.
You two do idol songs and stuff.
Are you familiar with it?
It's a mess.
For the record.
That's great.
we
Idol of Youth
What kind of idols did you like in your youth?
Ryoko Hirosue
Idol.
Yes.
Why can't it sink this low?
You're calling me a liar.
The Dark Side of Television
By the way, do you know about first love cider?
I don't know
First Love Cider
Sakai has a tattoo on his back that says "first love.
Cider on my back.
Love really does pop, doesn't it?
I'm just saying.
Let's go.
First, at the 2016 Idol Fest.
An unprecedented psyllium-throwing incident broke out.
A legendary song is back tonight!
Baby Rays Japan.
Dawn Brand New Days
The first is Rainbow Conquistadors.
Riko Shimizu
Called one of the best singers in the idol world.
Dreaming of becoming an ani-song singer
What is the ability of the singing Uta Hime?
It's a world of nothing.
The second is Aki Toyonaga from HKT48.
In the AKB Group Singing Ability Number One Contest
The beautiful voice of this talented artist, who has made it to the finals, is a source of pride.
traveling inspectors sent by the Shogun in the Edo period
Even in a world of nothing, with you around, it's Shiny Days.
I'll never forget how far away it was. Or how many.
Subtitle Kiminomiya
Even in an ordinary world, it's Shining day when you're around.
I'll never forget that no matter how far away we get, we're going to win.
The fourth person is Philosophy Dance Hinata Haru.
Amazing soulful voice coming from a small body
Get intoxicated by the soulful one-liners of a powerful diva who is the pride of the idol world.
Subtitle Kiminomiya
Even in an ordinary world, if you're here, it's Shining Days.
No matter how far away it gets, even Gerson won't forget it.
Then the second song was Idol of Idol
Many people were overwhelmed by Airi Suzuki's singing.
The most covered divine song by idols
Bono's First Love Cider
I'll give you a kiss, a thought I just realized
Because no words will ever be enough.
Subtitle Kiminomiya
I'll give it to you for a kiss, because if you realize it now, all kinds of words won't suffice.
Thank you for watching!
I'll give you a kiss, a thought I just realized
Because no words will ever be enough.
Subtitle Kiminomiya
I'll remove the kisses, the feelings I just realized.
Because no words are ever enough.
Every day there is a battle you can never lose. Last prize race of the weekday! Everyday prize race!
Programming suit by hero!
I've never been in this MC seat so properly before.
It can get all bent out of shape.
What's wrong with that?
Thank God, it's Akari Suda.
Are you sure? Are you sure?
That's insanely helpful.
It's got a kind of cozy look to it.
Maybe he was around here somewhere.
Tell him I have great astigmatism.
You were there?
You're a handshake legend, aren't you?
I'm not a legend at all.
You were kind of tenacious.
persistently
That kind of enveloping handshake.
no, really
He said either Akari Suda or Bongo's mother.
Bongo's mom?
Onigiri?
Now then, my idols, this way please.
Here you go.
please
It was fun.
Excellent performance
Oh, and there goes the adorable position.
Which one? Which one?
I think it's good to stand up.
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Everyone will scatter in whichever direction they like.
thank you for your efforts
Soyu seems to be going to slay a mammoth.
That's right, now go out there and fight.
me
So that's what we're doing, that's what we're doing.
Now that could be reflected in the score.
Now then, Suda-san, please announce the scores for the first round.
Here are the scores for the first round
9 points 9 points 9 points 9 points 10 points
I need a ten.
Thank you.
Mammoth is not on point at all.
It's no thanks to the mammoths.
I'm not in it at all.
It's called that soulful voice.
I don't think there are many idols who can go that far.
At the BBB in Unexpectedness
We were able to go through it.
Thank you.
How was the top batter?
I mean, do you remember me?
What do you think anything is?
That's it, isn't it?
It's the rainbow road of Mario cards, right?
not match the correct (answer, etc.)
Yeah, that's what I meant.
No, I slept with three guests on the radio.
I remember.
I know! I know!
I'm serious. I remember.
seriously
It's kind of embarrassing, so don't be like that.
I'm too embarrassed to remember how stiff I was.
Good for you.
How was it?
Yes, I like SK48.
I liked Akari Suda.
Thank you.
I sang Hatsukoi Side for Akari Suda today.
All right.
It was meant for me.
It was a two-push.
Two pushes, oh no, one push is
Julina Matsui.
Juli Juli.
Seniors.
The theme of the second round was
Show off your cuteness.
yeah
Today's Idol Buzz Song.
Yes, sir.
Idol Buzz Songs
What do you think about Idol Buzz Songs?
Now, of course, the same is true for CDs.
In this age of social networking, we can send out information to the world.
The buzz is not limited to Japan.
This may be the most important part for idols nowadays.
The whole world could be watching this moment.
Hey, stop laughing on the floor when I talk about my idols.
What the hell do you know about it?
Let's go.
First of all, the idols who got a lot of buzz on TikTok this year are
The hottest song that everyone is dancing to
The superlative cutest of the super crush publicity department.
You dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
If you release the most crush in your history, it's the cutest thing ever.
Admit it, this is the damsel in distress.
You dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
The most dokimeki release in my history is the most adorable.
Admit it, this is the damsel in distress.
You dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
The most exciting release in my history
It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Admit it, the damsel strikes back.
You dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
The most exciting summer in my history is the most adorable summer ever.
Don't stop to look, but this is the damsel in distress.
Then a storm between the lines from all the dollar-otas
Unprecedented song condensing goals gets demon buzz on TikTok
iLife's Idol Life Start Attack
Time never stops.
I'll transfer on the trip. I'll transfer so much.
Suddenly quiet and silent attack.
Yell love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Come on, fly, burning shallows, reddened bells
Late is when you're twenty.
This is the future. The play sings.
Oh yeah!
Cut! Cut! Us and Your Love
Dollar Lala Life
Wow!
Oh!
The moon never stops.
I'll transfer on the trip. I'll transfer so much.
Suddenly quiet nothing.
man who dances with the clouds
If you get in someone's way, you'll get out of it.
Hey, shout out! Sellout!
Crawl in bed.
burning red eyes
be fast asleep (and totally unaware of what is going on around one)
I've been drinking since I turned 20.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
title that can be tucked away
Oh yeah
Lala Lala, us and your love
Lulu Lala Life
Wow!
Good stuff.
The sun never stops shining.
Me too.
I'll transfer it in. I'll transfer it in so much.
Suddenly quiet.
relax one's mind
When the wind blows
Shout out Oi, Uriah, Oi.
SAKUME
Burning redfish
cheki rice Eating
I haven't had a drink in six months.
This is what makes life worth living.
I want to meet my sisters.
Oh yeah
The wig, us and your love
Dralalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaala
boo (wrong answer, like buzzer on quiz shows)
Oh, my gosh.
amazing
Thank you for watching!
Time never stops.
Pendulum on a journey Pendulum
Suddenly it gets quiet and they dance in silence.
One at a time, I'll holler. Hey, sell it, sell it.
Seino Desert Way by Burning Morning
I didn't start drinking and eating daikon until I was twenty.
This is what I didn't expect. The sisters start singing.
Now let's get on with ours and your idyllic life.
yay
- This is great! - Fun!
- Wow! - Amazing!
- Oh, my God! - Sorry!
Amazing!!!
The expressions and even the age groups sound a bit different.
There are those who say the company's lines in a certain tone, and those who shift them a little and put them in a little song.
What did I say, what was it?
The moon never stops."
The Moon Never Stops" Oranar
It's super fun live!
Super fun it is!
And you know, you can do this "de" thing, too, with your uncle, who's a fan.
"Mmm."
Please announce the scores of the second round, Mr. Suda.
Here are the scores for the second round
action of quickly bowing or lowering one's head
Ooh.
That's a little different.
8,010 points8,009 points
Ooh.
I was allowed to do so.
That first song.
During that superlative cute.
After saying some kind of cute little lyrics.
Mr. Sakai almost drooled as he delivered his soundbite.
Yes, sir.
ah!
I like this first one.
Just make him forget. That's it.
That was just a curry, thinking there would only be 10 points left, and they just don't put as much effort into aviation anymore.
I could see that you were a little nervous.
I looked at it thinking, "You could do more.
I'm actually the type of person who is never made to do anything cute.
Twintails are prohibited.
I'd be so pissed if I wore twin tails.
I was like, "I want you to be cool.
I thought I'd do my best today to try to free you up a bit.
I was a little nervous.
It's beyond my expectation that I could make it prettier and prettier.
Thank you.
By the way...
Polish up this cuteness.
It's a bit of a technical part.
What are some of the things you keep in mind?
There is one thing.
Thinking you are the prettiest and most remarkable person in the world.
For example, even a single line, "Cururun.
If I were to tell the camera, which one would it be?
Girl wondering which one to choose.
then
We'll all be there.
purrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrm!
キュルルン キュルルン キュルルン
I did. I did them all.
Really, Mr. Tech, they're all laughing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're smiling.
Something's different.
Not what I expected.
Try that camera curlun from earlier.
You don't have to look back.
Let me do it.
Why do you accumulate it?
purrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrm!
cute
Cute.
I'll try to do as much as I can.
Me?
I'll do it?
Let's do one.
Ooh.
abbr. of particle "ni" (used especially when it precedes the verb "naru")
power
You lent me something.
Cururung Power
Is that what this is about?
We were all equally scarred.
Good, good, good.
That's a horizontal uniformity.
The theme of the third round is
Appeal to your ability to express yourself.
And I'm going to ask you to sing.
The idol god song of my dreams
I see
Let's go.
Riko Shimizu chose the song
Promise the Star at FISH
Emotions directly to the heart.
He says he loves the feeling.
Singing famous songs
That's all I have to say, and they'll understand.
Don't you think every time
Promise
Oh, great.
Toyoma then chose Morning Musume. Summer Night Town at
Morning Musume。ヌs group, which I fell in love with under the influence of my sister, who is a fan of Halo Pro. She sings the famous songs of the Morbs, the origin of her idol career.
Smile, smile, smile, don't stare at my lips.
They're going to read your mind.
I don't want to look like an adult with bad makeup.
one cannot hide one's heart
I hate it. I hate it. I hate it. I love it.
Next, Yuriya Dojo chose
Orchestra in BiSH
Memorable songs sung during auditions
A performance as passionate as that of BiSH, which I adore.
I'll never forget the way you laughed when we held hands.
I've made you cry so much, and your tears, and the sound of your voice, they're all gone.
Last, Hinata Haru chose "Akina Nakamori."
Tears are not for decoration.
My mother sang it to me when I was a little girl, ever since I can remember.
I'm going to challenge myself with a song from my memory that I can sing naturally.
It's not prudent, the tears.
I hope it's just beautiful.
It's just a little too sad, the tears.
difficult (e.g. customer, guest, child)
This is hard.
I'm in trouble.
I don't care if I'm being scolded by your offices.
I would love to go to karaoke.
I love it so much, I hate it so much, I hate it so much.
You made me do the mother part.
That's not fair.
I'm not on the girls' side, I'm the mother on the receiving end.
Now, the highest total score is currently 19 points for Mr. Toyonaga and Ms. Hyuga.
The total score of the three rounds will determine the winner.
And the other two are totally reversible.
Still available.
Come on, Mr. Suda, I know you're having trouble, but it's okay, take your time and think about it.
I'm very worried.
Cherry blossoms are not blooming well this year.
They're hooking me up.
Thank you.
In this cycle of cold and hot sometimes, humans are coming in after the fact on their own.
That could be done to Mother Nature.
There is an old man like this in the park.
I'll give you a ride to the station.
It's done.
I'm glad you called.
Thank you.
Now then, let's announce the scores for the third round.
Suda-san, please.
The scores in the third round were
This way.
10 points 10 points 9 points 9 points 9 points
What's going to happen to this?
So there you have it, the scores.
The highest total score of the three rounds was
Mr. Toyonaga 29 points
So congratulations to Mr. Toyonaga for this week's Mainichi Champion!
Thank you.
I'm sure there was some tension among the older members of the chocolate tribe, though.
I was thrilled, but very happy.
I'm also afraid that people will think I'm choosing them because we're in the same 48.
If you honestly put a score on each round.
He said he had no choice but to do this now.
Yes, it's the way you capture people's hearts and minds, and the unexpectedness of it all.
Overall, we have done this.
Wonderful congratulations!
Are you going to get hooked on idol songs?
No, I really liked that one.
That was a good one, Cole's.
Good call.
Everyone who wants to do this or that.
It's definitely a fun thing to do, I can tell.
It's very scary from the stage.
The kind they say in the dressing room?
Wasn't that one with the right leg a bit of a mess?
The one that people say is over.
Now then, the winner, Mr. Toyonaga.
In response to Suda-san's request to hear more
Could you please sing a song for us?
Thank you.
What song should we play?
I would like to sing the song "I want to go somewhere with you" by HKT48.
I see
May I have a phrase from the chorus?
What?
Oh, by all means!
I have to say so because my seniors say so.
That's nice.
Here you go.
omnibus
You don't have a lot of confidence.
The weatherman said it's going to be hot this summer.
Maybe I'll shorten my hair. You show the same.
We are always within arm's reach.
You can't start a relationship if you're too close.
I want to fly somewhere with you. Not here. Farther.
Let's get out of the routine. The tracks continue.
I wonder if I'll be scolded for stopping. I want to see the you that I don't know.
The sky outside my window is always a different color tomorrow than it is today.
Into a New World
hash belt
Oh no, it's a mess of good songs!
Thank you.
You... failed to catch the pitch.
Purposefully approaching idolatry.
I was listening to the sound.
He was cheating.
Technique.
When I was an idol
The kind where you can't get the microphone volume up very high.
If you're that type of person.
No, it was great, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Daily Show Race
NEXT WEEK
A battle we can never lose.
It happens every day.
Last show race on a weekday
Daily Show Race
produced by
hero